Time Bank
Brought to you by: Orange-Flash | Bit.ly/2HKzs60
Original air date: 1984.08.10
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Why are you laying idle?
I was asked to run an errand, but I came quickly to play with Shizuka-chan...
Do you have any homework to do?
Yes, I do.
So, why don't you do it now?
I'd rather do it after playing with Shizuka-chan.
Would you really have any time after that?
Don't worry.
What do you have after playing?
Now I remember! I want to watch Perman anime, today @6 PM.
Thanks!
After watching TV, it's dinner-time.
Mum said today she will make steak for dinner.
Then after dinner, it's bath-time.
Going to bathroom, changing clothes it will be about 9PM.
Then it's sleep-time!
I'll do it definitely.
You mean it?
I wish mum returns ASAP.
Ah! What a waste of time!
You have to spend the time meaningfully.
That's it!
Here's Time Bank.
It enables one to manipulate the spare time however one wants.
Slow-down or speed-up the time?
Your mum said she'll be back by 3:00 PM.
Now it's 2:30 PM, so I'm going deposit the remaining 30 minutes into Time Bank.
Pressing this button will save 30 minutes into it.
Save 30 minutes.
Thanks for the transaction. I've took care of your 30 minutes.
Now 30 minutes have passed. Look at your clock.
True, it's now become 3:00 PM
I'm back home!
Mum's back.
If you leave it like this, homework time